Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Legal Department Records, 1956-1986; 28274
  - DC 37 v. SIC: Transcripts, 1981; cuid5088; 28394 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Executive Orders (Mayoral), 1973-1980; cuid5089; 28393 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Legal Notes and Memoranda, 1978; cuid5090; 28392 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Proposed Legislation I, 1978; cuid5091; 28391 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Financial Emergency Act: Proposed Legislation II, 1978; cuid5092; 28390 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Fiscal Crisis: Effect on Women and Minorities, 1976; cuid5093; 28389 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee: DC 37 Merger, 1956-1957; cuid5094; 28388 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Background Materials, 1967-1977; cuid5095; 28387 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Correspondence, 1977-1978; cuid5096; 28386 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Legal Papers, 1977-1978; cuid5097; 28385 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Notes, ca.1977; cuid5098; 28384 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Local 211 (Allied Building Inspectors Union) Summer Hours Arbitration: Transcripts, 1977; cuid5099; 28383 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Local 371 (SSEU) v. Adam Walinsky, Chairman of SIC, 1981; cuid5100; 28382 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, 1976, 1979; cuid5101; 28381 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, Background Materials I, 1957-1980; cuid5102; 28380 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Disaffiliation Proposal, Background Materials II, 1957-1980; cuid5103; 28379 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Legal Papers, 1974-1978; cuid5104; 28378 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Local 2021 (OTB): Arbitration of Grievance, 1981; cuid5105; 28377 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Mando, Daniel J., et al. v. Abraham Beame, et al. (Emergency Employment Act Employees Case): Briefs and Memoranda of Law, 1975; cuid5106; 28376 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Mando v. Beame: Correspondence, 1974-1977; cuid5107; 28375 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits I, 1971-1974; cuid5108; 28374 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits II, 1971-1974; cuid5109; 28373 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits III, 1971-1974; cuid5110; 28372 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits IV, 1971-1974; cuid5111; 28371 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Mando v. Beame: Exhibits V, 1971-1974; cuid5112; 28370 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Mando v. Beame: Extra Legal, 1974-1976; cuid5113; 28369 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Mando v. Beame: Factual, 1971-1974; cuid5114; 28368 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Mando v. Beame: Notes and Memoranda, 1974; cuid5115; 28367 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings I, 1972-1974; cuid5116; 28366 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings II, 1972-1974; cuid5117; 28365 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mando v. Beame: Pleadings III, 1972-1974; cuid5118; 28364 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Mando v. Beame: Transcripts, 1974; cuid5119; 28363 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - MENTOR Program (MELS and Board of Education), 1984; cuid5120; 28362 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - MENTOR Program (MELS and Board of Education): Printed Material, undated; cuid5121; 28361 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Middlebrooks, et al. v. NYPD (Police Aides Case): Charts and Statistical Analysis, 1976-1979; cuid5122; 28360 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Documents and Exhibits, 1978-1980; cuid5123; 28359 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Formal Papers, 1980-1981; cuid5124; 28358 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Labor-Management Meeting, 1980; cuid5125; 28357 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Legal Research, 1975-1979; cuid5126; 28356 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Notes, ca.1980; cuid5127; 28355 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Statistics on Coverage, 1979; cuid5128; 28354 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Middebrooks v. NYPD: Witnesses, 1979; cuid5129; 28353 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - New York City Board of Education: CETA Titles, 1975; cuid5130; 28352 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - New York City Board of Education: Improper Labor Practices, 1976; cuid5131; 28351 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - New York City Board of Education: Stavisky-Goodman Litigation, 1976-1980; cuid5132; 28350 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation HHC: Conflict of Interest Cases, 1979; cuid5133; 28349 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1970-1976; cuid5134; 28348 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1977-1978; cuid5135; 28347 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - New York City HHC: General Legal, 1979-1984; cuid5136; 28346 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - New York Police Department: Improper Labor Practices, 1979-1980; cuid5137; 28345 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Parking Violations Bureau, 1979; cuid5138; 28344 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME et al. v. State of Washington, Clippings, 1983-1984; cuid5139; 28343 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Comparable Worth Studies, 1974, 1976; cuid5140; 28342 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Petition for En Banc Hearing, 1985; cuid5141; 28341 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Pleadings, 1983-1985; cuid5142; 28340 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Press Releases, 1982-1985; cuid5143; 28339 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME v. Washington, Settlement, 1985; cuid5144; 28338 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME Publications, undated, 1980-1981; cuid5145; 28337 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Pay Equity: AFSCME Research Department Reports, 1982-1983; cuid5146; 28336 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Pay Equity: Chicago, AFSCME EEOC Filing, 1983; cuid5147; 28335 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Articles I, undated, 1980-1986; cuid5148; 28334 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Articles II, undated, 1980-1986; cuid5149; 28333 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Pay Equity: Comparable Worth Research Materials, 1980-1986; cuid5150; 28332 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Pay Equity: Gold, Michael Evans, "A Dialogue on Comparable Worth", 1984; cuid5151; 28331 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Pay Equity: Gross, Beverly, 1984-1985; cuid5152; 28330 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Pay Equity: Law Review Articles, 1982-1985; cuid5153; 28329 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Pay Equity: Los Angeles County Employees, SEIU Report, 1985; cuid5154; 28328 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Pay Equity: Minnesota Department of Employee Relations, Local Government Pay Equity Supplement for Cities, 1984; cuid5155; 28327 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Pay Equity: New York City, 1982-1985; cuid5156; 28326 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Pay Equity: New York City Office of the Mayor, Report on Status of Women in NYC Government, 1971; cuid5157; 28325 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Pay Equity: New York State Comparable Worth Study by Center for Women in Government, 1985; cuid5158; 28324 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Pay Equity: New York State Division of Human Rights, 1985; cuid5159; 28323 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Pay Equity: Newman, Winn Articles and Statements, undated, 1981-1985; cuid5160; 28322 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Pay Equity: Printed Material (Various Organizations), 1979-1985; cuid5161; 28321 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. Commission on Civil Rights Reports, 1984; cuid5162; 28320 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, Winn Newman Testimony, 1984; cuid5163; 28319 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity: U.S. General Accounting Office, Status of State Activities on Pay Equity, 1986; cuid5164; 28318 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity: Women's Advocacy Committee of New York, Study on Women in NYC Government (Clerical Workers), 1972; cuid5165; 28317 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Santos, Rafael v. Security and Law Enforcement Employees, 1978-1978; cuid5166; 28316 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Santos, Rafael v. Security and Law Enforcement Employees: Background Materials, undated; cuid5167; 28315 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - School Breakfast Program, 1976-1977; cuid5168; 28314 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - School Breakfast Program: Community School Board Lists/Compliance, 1976; cuid5169; 28313 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - School Breakfast Program: Response to Demand Letter, 1976; cuid5170; 28312 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - School Breakfast Program: Legal Research, 1974-1976; cuid5171; 28311 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Tellez, Rogelio v. City of New York, 1975-1982; cuid5172; 28310 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Wage Controls, 1976; cuid5173; 28309 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor: Bargaining Rights, 1977; cuid5174; 28308 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Women in City Government United, et al. v. City of New York, et al.: Administrative, 1977-1983; cuid5175; 28307 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, 1973, 1976-1977, 1980; cuid5176; 28306 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Legal, undated, 1971-1979; cuid5177; 28305 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Legislation, 1971, 1973; cuid5178; 28304 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Pension Plan, 1969-1970; cuid5179; 28303 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Background Materials, Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA), 1975, 1981-1982; cuid5180; 28302 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Change of Attorney, 1977; cuid5181; 28301 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Class Action Status, 1975-1976; cuid5182; 28300 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Clippings, 1973-1980; cuid5183; 28299 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Correspondence I, 1973-1983; cuid5184; 28298 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Correspondence II, 1973-1983; cuid5185; 28297 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Internal Memoranda, 1973-1976; cuid5186; 28296 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories I, 1975-1977, 1980; cuid5187; 28295 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories II, 1975-1977, 1980; cuid5188; 28294 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Interrogatories III, 1975-1977, 1980; cuid5189; 28293 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Kinzel Commission Reports, 1976; cuid5190; 28292 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda I, 1975-1978, 1980-1982; cuid5191; 28291 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda II, 1975-1978, 1980-1982; cuid5192; 28290 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Memoranda III, 1975-1978, 1980-1982; cuid5193; 28289 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Motion for Summary Judgment, 1980; cuid5194; 28288 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Notes, 1976-1979; cuid5195; 28287 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Notice to Admit and Responses, 1976-1977, 1980; cuid5196; 28286 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Order to Show Cause, 1980; cuid5197; 28285 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings I, 1975-1982; cuid5198; 28284 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings II, 1975-1982; cuid5199; 28283 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Pleadings III, 1975-1982; cuid5200; 28282 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Program Planners Analysis, 1976; cuid5201; 28281 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Settlement Proposals I, 1977-1980; cuid5202; 28280 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Settlement Proposals II, 1977-1980; cuid5203; 28279 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Stipulations, 1975-1977, 1979-1980; cuid5204; 28278 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Women in City Government v. NYC: Transport Workers Union Case (Burns, Jackson, Miller, Summit, and Spitzer v. Lindner), MLC Amicus Curiae, undated; cuid5205; 28277 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Workers' Compensation, 1977-1984; cuid5206; 28276 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Youth Employment Act: Young Adult Conservation Corps, 1978; cuid5207; 28275 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Communications Department Records, 1963-2004; 28115
  - Subseries IV:A: Edward Handman Records, 1972-1991., 28220
    - City Budget: Clippings, 1978-1980; cuid5208; 28273 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Common Retirement Fund, 1981; cuid5209; 28272 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1980, 1987, 1990-1991; cuid5210; 28271 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1977-1978; cuid5211; 28270 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1979-1980; cuid5212; 28269 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Contract Negotiations: Clippings, 1987, 1990; cuid5213; 28268 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Contract Negotiations: Municipal Labor Committee Campaign, 1987; cuid5214; 28267 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: General, 1983-1989; cuid5215; 28266 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - DC 37 Film Strip, 1989; cuid5216; 28265 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions", 1985; cuid5217; 28264 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions": Correspondence, 1985-1986; cuid5218; 28263 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - DC 37/AFL-CIO Conference: "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions": Transcript, 1985; cuid5219; 28262 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Chronology, 1974-1977; cuid5220; 28261 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, undated; cuid5221; 28260 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, 1973-1974; cuid5222; 28259 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, Jan 1975-Jul 1975; cuid5223; 28258 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, Aug 1975-Dec 1975; cuid5224; 28257 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Clippings, 1976-1977; cuid5225; 28256 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): General, 1975-1976; cuid5226; 28255 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1975): Municipal Labor Committee Reports, ca.1976; cuid5227; 28254 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, undated; cuid5228; 28253 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Oct 1990-Nov 1990; cuid5229; 28252 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Dec 1990-Jan 1991; cuid5230; 28251 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Feb 1991-Mar 1991; cuid5231; 28250 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Apr 1991; cuid5232; 28249 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, May 1, 1991-May 15, 1991; cuid5233; 28248 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, May 16, 1991-May 31, 1991; cuid5234; 28247 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jun 1, 1991-Jun 20, 1991; cuid5235; 28246 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jun 21, 1991-Jun 30, 1991; cuid5236; 28245 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Clippings, Jul 1991-Aug 1991; cuid5237; 28244 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, 1990; cuid5238; 28243 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, Jan 1991-Mar 1991; cuid5239; 28242 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): General, Apr 1991-Jun 1991; cuid5240; 28241 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Fiscal Crisis (1991): Library Budget Cuts, cuid5241; 28240 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Handman, Edward: Biographical Information, undated; cuid5242; 28239 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Handman, Edward: Book Proposal, undated; cuid5243; 28238 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Handman, Edward: Journalism Syllabi, undated; cuid5244; 28237 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Handman, Edward: Op-Ed Articles, undated; cuid5245; 28236 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Handman, Edward: Op-Ed Articles, 1984-1990; cuid5246; 28235 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Handman, Edward: Testimony on State Government, 1987; cuid5247; 28234 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - It's Your City, It's Our Job Radio Show: Journalism Contests, 1988-1989; cuid5248; 28233 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - It's Your City, It's Our Job Radio Show Transcripts (Domestic Violence; Staten Island; Homeless), 1987-1989; cuid5249; 28232 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Labor Movement: Clippings, 1985-1986; cuid5250; 28231 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Labor-Management Articles, undated, 1985, 1988; cuid5251; 28230 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - March on Washington for Jobs and Job Security, 1975; cuid5252; 28229 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - March on Washington for Jobs and Job Security: Clippings, 1975; cuid5253; 28228 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Political Action: Mayoral Campaign (Dinkins), 1990; cuid5254; 28227 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Mondale-Ferraro), 1984; cuid5255; 28226 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Public Relations Campaign, undated, 1972, 1986-1988; cuid5256; 28225 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Reagan Budget: Clippings, 1984; cuid5257; 28224 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Reagan Budget: Impact on New York City, 1980-1984; cuid5258; 28223 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Williams, Franklin: Commentaries, 1983; cuid5259; 28222 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Window Guard Campaign, 1981; cuid5260; 28221 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Subseries IV:B: Bill Schleicher Records, 1992-2004., 28146
    - AFSCME Convention (36th), 2004; cuid5261; 28219 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Bargaining: Notes, 2003; cuid5262; 28218 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Black History Month, 2004; cuid5263; 28217 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Blackout (Con Edison), 2003; cuid5264; 28216 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Building-Wide Meetings: Notes, 2003; cuid5265; 28215 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - City Budget, 2004; cuid5266; 28214 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - City Budget: Child Health Nurses, 2003-2004; cuid5267; 28213 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 2002-2004; cuid5268; 28212 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Contract Negotiations, 2004; cuid5269; 28211 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Contract Negotiations: Fair Contract Rally, 2003; cuid5270; 28210 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: AFSCME, Insurance Fraud Claims, 2000; cuid5271; 28209 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Albert Diop and Martin Lubin Clippings, 1998, 2000; cuid5272; 28208 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Annual Return/Report of Employee Benefit Plan, 1992-1993; cuid5273; 28207 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Clippings and Articles, 1997-2000; cuid5274; 28206 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Correspondence, 1995-2000; cuid5275; 28205 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Financial Statements, 1996-1999; cuid5276; 28204 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Harold Hawson and Anthony Lawson v. DC 37 et al., 1999-2000; cuid5277; 28203 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Judicial Panel Decisions, 1999-2000; cuid5278; 28202 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 1 of 3, I, 2001; cuid5279; 28201 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 1 of 3, II, 2001; cuid5280; 28200 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 2 of 3, 2001; cuid5281; 28199 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "Report on Certain Financial Activities at AFSCME DC 37 and Funds" Book 3 of 3, 2001; cuid5282; 28198 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: KPMG, "The Ratification Vote on the 1995 Economic Agreement: A Report to the General Council of AFSCME", 1999; cuid5283; 28197 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Labor Organization Annual Reports, 1989-1998; cuid5284; 28196 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Legal Transcripts, 2000; cuid5285; 28195 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Notes, 1999; cuid5286; 28194 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Press Releases, 1999-2001; cuid5287; 28193 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Printed Material, 1999-2000; cuid5288; 28192 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Reform Proposals, 2000; cuid5289; 28191 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Contract Ratification Vote Scandal: Union Democracy Articles, 1998-1999; cuid5290; 28190 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: General, 2001-2003; cuid5291; 28189 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Delegate Education, 2003; cuid5292; 28188 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Delegates: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004; cuid5293; 28187 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Direct Election of Officers Dispute: Veronica Montgomery-Costa Testimony, 2004; cuid5294; 28186 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Editorials: Source Material, 2004; cuid5295; 28185 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Executive Board: Meeting Notes, 2001-2002; cuid5296; 28184 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Executive Board: Meeting Notes, 2003-2004; cuid5297; 28183 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Event Announcements: DC 37, 2003-2004; cuid5298; 28182 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Event Announcements: Other Organizations, 2003-2004; cuid5299; 28181 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Finances: Corruption Scandals, 2002-2003; cuid5300; 28180 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports, 2003-2004; cuid5301; 28179 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Grassroots Lobby Institute: Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5302; 28178 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Group Leaders: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004; cuid5303; 28177 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, Nov 2001-Feb 2002; cuid5304; 28176 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, May 2002-Feb 2003; cuid5305; 28175 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Group Leaders: Reports, Apr 2003-Sep 2004; cuid5306; 28174 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Health Care Benefits and Prescription Drug Coverage, 2003; cuid5307; 28173 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Immigrant Worker Freedom Ride, 2003; cuid5308; 28172 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - International Human Rights Day: AFL-CIO March, 2003; cuid5309; 28171 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Iraq War, 2004; cuid5310; 28170 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Labor Day, 2004; cuid5311; 28169 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) Dispute: People of the State of New York v. Charles Hughes and Mildred Stephens, ca.1999; cuid5312; 28168 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) Dispute: People of the State of New York v. Martin Hughes, Joseph Alfano, James Rose, and Richard Lewis, ca.1999; cuid5313; 28167 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Local 375 (CSTG) Dispute: CSTG v. DC 37, 1999; cuid5314; 28166 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Urban Park Rangers Retirement Program, 2003; cuid5315; 28165 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Local Presidents: Meeting Notes, 2001-2004; cuid5316; 28164 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Medicaid Budget Cuts, 2004; cuid5317; 28163 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC): Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5318; 28162 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 2003; cuid5319; 28161 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - New York State AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention, 1996; cuid5320; 28160 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Officer Structure, 1999; cuid5321; 28159 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Per Diem Employees, 2002-2003; cuid5322; 28158 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Pinkett, Mary: Death of, 2003; cuid5323; 28157 (Box 42, Folder 27)